Xi Zhou
希舟
Xu Jinfeng
徐津枫
Yulu changed his words: Very handsome and sunny
玉露改词：挺帅的 很阳光
The kind of boy who will be very popular wherever he puts it
那种放在哪都会很有人气的男生
Ah Feng
阿枫
I bought food and came back
我买吃的回来了
Why did you go to buy it specially
怎么还特意去买
We just got busy, why don't we have a midnight snack together
我们刚忙完要不一起吃个宵夜吧
Auntie, you haven't been to the company since you came so far
阿姨您这么远来 还没来过公司
Why don't you have dinner together
要不然一起吃个饭吧
Oh, I won't join in the fun when you young people eat
哎呀你们年轻人吃饭我就不凑热闹了
Quick baby
快快 宝贝
Don't let someone else treat you
别让别人请客哦
Just treat your mother and eat well
就当妈妈请客了吃好哦
Bye bye
拜拜
Go away
走了
Sister, my lifelong happiness
姐妹 我的终身幸福
It's up to you
就要靠你了
Am I trying to help you sabotage
我这不正在努力帮你搞破坏吗
Not Xu Jinfeng
不是徐津枫
They're not really brothers
他俩其实不是亲兄弟
The handsome boy is nominally Xu Jinfeng's eldest brother
大帅哥名义上是徐津枫的大哥
Actually, it is the adopted son of the Xu family
实际上是徐家的养子
That year, Xu Jinfeng's parents had a car accident
那年啊徐津枫父母出车祸
It was a car accident. He was in the car.
车祸啊他当时也在车上
He was in the car, too
他当时也在车上
No wonder you said you were scared in the elevator just now
怪不得你说刚才在电梯里给你吓够呛
It is estimated that it was the shadow left at that time
估计就是当时留下的阴影
Hey
哎
You said
你说
Xu Nanfeng, a handsome boy, is the child of their driver
大帅哥徐楠风是他们家司机的孩子
The driver was adopted by the Xu family after his death
司机去世之后被徐家收养
Xu Jinfeng studied abroad all the year round
徐津枫 常年在国外留学
The company is managed by Xu Nanfeng
公司都由徐楠风管理
Isn't this the script of Ba Zong Nan Er
这不就是霸总男二的剧本吗
But you have the script of the chosen woman
可你拿的是天选之女大女主的剧本
Are you sure you two are right
确定你俩对的上吗
How do you know if you don't try
不试试怎么知道啊
Hello, Miss Lin
喂 林小姐
Boss
老板
Yulu changed its words: A customer wants to talk to the person in charge of the business. Look
玉露改词：有位客户想找业务负责人面谈您看
Yulu changed its words: Is it convenient for you to see it
玉露改词：您方便见一下吗
Okay, I see
行我知道了
Done
搞定
Is there anything wrong with the company
公司有什么事吗
Xu Nanfeng changed his words; Miss Lin asked me to pick up clients at the company
徐楠枫改词；林小姐让我去公司接一下客户
Then she won't come today, will she
那她今天是不过来了吧
I forgot if you didn't tell me
你不说我都忘了
The company OA has an application for leave
公司OA有一条请假申请
It should be to see that I haven't approved it yet
应该是看我还没有批
Call specially to rush it
特地打电话催一下吧
Leave OA
请假OA
Miss Chiang
蒋小姐
The customer Miss Lin said is yours
林  小姐说的客户就是您的
Mr. Xu, what about the information you want
徐总您要的资料呢
It's in my company
就在我公司
Would you please make a run
麻烦您跑一趟
No problem
没问题
Hey, I reported your car violation
哎你的车违停被我举报了
Just now
就刚才
Take my car
坐我车
Row
行
What to do
怎么办
The project exhibition is today
项目展示会就在今天
I seem to have a fever
好像发烧了
Hello
喂
I'm afraid I have a fever
我好像发烧了
Ah, what about that
啊 那怎么办
Such an important customer today
今天这么重要的客户
Have you prepared all the materials for the project exhibition
项目展示会的资料都准备好了吗
You ask the boss for leave first
你先跟老板请假
I'll find a way to explain the plan here
方案讲解这边我来想办法
Good
好
All the materials for the afternoon exhibition are here
下午展示会的资料都在这了
Do you see anything to add
你看有什么要补充的
This exhibition is very important
这次展示会非常重要
Don't make any mistakes
千万不能出差错
The above is the general situation of this project
以上呢就是这个项目的大致情况
What is the original design concept of this project
请问这个项目的原始设计理念是
We use chain design
我们用连锁设计的
This character is called Youni
这个人物叫做悠尼
Because when Qin Shihuang built the Terracotta Warriors and Horses,
因为秦始皇当年打造兵马俑的时候
Excuse me
不好意思
I have something urgent at home
我家中有些急事
Next, the vice president will explain to you
接下来呢由副总裁向您进行阐述